breach.tv 2019-08-12

# Privacy Policy - Breach TV

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
 _Last updated January 24, 2019_  
Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at Breach Media Services (“Company”, “we”, “us”, or  
“our”). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any  
questions or concerns about our policy, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please  
contact us at richard.adams@breach.tv.  
When you visit our website [www.breach.tv](http://www.breach.tv/), and use our services, you trust us with your personal  
information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we describe our privacy policy. We  
seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what  
rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important.  
If there are any terms in this privacy policy that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Sites  
and our services.  
This privacy policy applies to all information collected through our website (such as [www.breach.tv](http://www.breach.tv/)), and/or  
any related services, sales, marketing or events (we refer to them collectively in this privacy policy as the  
"Sites").  
Please read this privacy policy carefully as it will help you make informed decisions about sharing  
your personal information with us.  
 **  
TABLE OF CONTENTS**  
1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?  
2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?  
3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?  
4\. WHO WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH?  
5\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?  
6\. HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?  
7\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?  
8\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?  
9\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?  
10\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?  
11\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?  
12\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES  
13\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?  
14\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?  
15\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?  
 **  
1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**  
Personal information you disclose to us  
In Short: We collect personal information that you provide to us such as name, address, contact  
information, passwords and security data, payment information, and social media login data.  
We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when registering at the Sites expressing  
an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and services, when participating in activities  
on the Sites (such as posting messages in our online forums or entering competitions, contests or  
giveaways) or otherwise contacting us.  
The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Sites,  
the choices you make and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect can  
include the following:  
Name and Contact Data. We collect your first and last name, email address, postal address, phone  
number, and other similar contact data.  
Credentials. We collect passwords, password hints, and similar security information used for  
authentication and account access.  
Payment Data. We collect data necessary to process your payment if you make purchases, such as your  
payment instrument number (such as a credit card number), and the security code associated with your  
payment instrument. All payment data is stored by our payment processor and you should review its  
privacy policies and contact the payment processor directly to respond to your questions.  
Social Media Login Data. We provide you with the option to register using social media account details,  
like your Facebook, Twitter or other social media account. If you choose to register in this way, we will  
collect the Information described in the section called "HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS "  
below.  
All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete and accurate, and you must notify us  
of any changes to such personal information.  
Information automatically collected  
In Short: Some information – such as IP address and/or browser and device characteristics – is collected  
automatically when you visit our Sites.  
We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Sites. This information  
does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and  
usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system,  
language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when  
you use our Sites and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the  
security and operation of our Sites, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.  
Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.  
Information collected from other sources  
In Short: We may collect limited data from public databases, marketing partners, social media platforms,  
and other outside sources.  
We may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing  
partners, social media platforms (such as Facebook), as well as from other third parties. Examples of the  
information we receive from other sources include: social media profile information (your name, gender,  
birthday, email, current city, state and country, user identification numbers for your contacts, profile picture  
URL and any other information that you choose to make public); marketing leads and search results and  
links, including paid listings (such as sponsored links).

 **2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**  
In Short: We process your information for purposes based on legitimate business interests, the fulfillment  
of our contract with you, compliance with our legal obligations, and/or your consent.  
We use personal information collected via our Sites for a variety of business purposes described below.  
We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests,  
in order to enter into or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal  
obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below.  
We use the information we collect or receive:  
To facilitate account creation and logon process. If you choose to link your account with us to a  
third party account *(such as your Google or Facebook account), we use the information you allowed  
us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and logon process. See the section  
below headed " HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS " for further information.  
To send you marketing and promotional communications. We and/or our third party marketing  
partners may use the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in  
accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt-out of our marketing emails at any time  
(see the " WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS " below).  
To send administrative information to you. We may use your personal information to send you  
product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms,  
conditions, and policies.  
Deliver targeted advertising to you. We may use your information to develop and display content  
and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and  
to measure its effectiveness.  
To enable user-to-user communications. We may use your information in order to enable user-to-user  
communications with each user's consent.  
To enforce our terms, conditions and policies.  
To respond to legal requests and prevent harm. If we receive a subpoena or other legal request,  
we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.  
For other Business Purposes. We may use your information for other Business Purposes, such as  
data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns  
and to evaluate and improve our Sites, products, services, marketing and your  
experience.

 **3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?**  
In Short: We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to protect your rights, or to  
fulfill business obligations.

We may process or share data based on the following legal basis:  
Consent: We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal  
information in a specific purpose.  
Legitimate Interests: We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our  
legitimate business interests.  
Performance of a Contract: Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your  
personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.  
Legal Obligations: We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in  
order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or  
legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public  
authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).  
Vital Interests: We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate,  
prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations  
involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation  
in which we are involved.  
More specifically, we may need to process your data or share your personal information in the following  
situations:  
Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers. We may share your data with  
third party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our  
behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: payment  
processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts.  
We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Sites, which will enable them  
to collect data about how you interact with the Sites over time. This information may be used to,  
among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better  
understand online activity. Unless described in this Policy, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of  
your information with third parties for their promotional purposes.  
Business Transfers. We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during  
negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of  
our business to another company.

 **4\. WHO WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH?**  
In Short: We only share information with the following third parties.

We only share and disclose your information with the following third parties. We have categorized each  
party so that you may be easily understand the purpose of our data collection and processing practices. If  
we have processed your data based on your consent and you wish to revoke your consent, please contact  
us.

Advertising, Direct Marketing, and Lead Generation  
Google AdSense, One by AOL and beachfront.io  
Allow Users to Connect to their Third-Party Accounts  
and Facebook account

Invoice and Billing  
PayPal, Venmo and Apple Pay

Social Media Sharing and Advertising  
Facebook social plugins, Twitter social plugins and Google+ social plugins

User Account Registration and Authentication  
Facebook Login

Web and Mobile Analytics  
Google Analytics

 **5\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?**  
In Short: We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information.

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store  
information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain  
cookies is set out in our Cookie Policy.

 **6\. HOW DO WE HANDLE YOUR SOCIAL LOGINS?**  
In Short: If you choose to register or log in to our websites using a social media account, we may have  
access to certain information about you.

Our Sites offer you the ability to register and login using your third party social media account details (like  
your Facebook or Twitter logins). Where you choose to do this, we will receive certain profile information  
about you from your social media provider. The profile Information we receive may vary depending on the  
social media provider concerned, but will often include your name, e-mail address, friends list, profile  
picture as well as other information you choose to make public.  
We will use the information we receive only for the purposes that are described in this privacy policy or that  
are otherwise made clear to you on the Sites. Please note that we do not control, and are not responsible  
for, other uses of your personal information by your third party social media provider. We recommend that  
you review their privacy policy to understand how they collect, use and share your personal information,  
and how you can set your privacy preferences on their sites and apps.

 **7\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?**  
In Short: We are not responsible for the safety of any information that you share with third-party providers  
who advertise, but are not affiliated with, our websites.

The Sites may contain advertisements from third parties that are not affiliated with us and which may link to  
other websites, online services or mobile applications. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data  
you provide to any third parties. Any data collected by third parties is not covered by this privacy policy. We  
are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties,  
including other websites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Sites. You should review  
the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.

 **8\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**  
In Short: We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy  
policy unless otherwise required by law.

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this  
privacy policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or  
other legal requirements). No purpose in this policy will require us keeping your personal information for  
longer than the period of time in which users have an account with us.  
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either  
delete or anonymize it, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been  
stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any  
further processing until deletion is possible.

 **9\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?**  
In Short: We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organizational and technical  
security measures.

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the  
security of any personal information we process. However, please also remember that we cannot  
guarantee that the internet itself is 100% secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal  
information, transmission of personal information to and from our Sites is at your own risk. You should only  
access the services within a secure environment.

 **10\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?**  
In Short: We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age.

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Sites, you  
represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to  
such minor dependent’s use of the Sites. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18  
years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly  
delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under  
age 18, please contact us at richard.adams@breach.tv.

 **11\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?**  
In Short: In some regions, such as the European Economic Area, you have rights that allow you greater  
access to and control over your personal information. You may review, change, or terminate your account  
at any time.  
In some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data  
protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal  
information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal  
information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right  
to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please use the contact  
details provided below. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data  
protection laws.  
If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, you have the right to withdraw your  
consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its  
withdrawal.  
If you are resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are unlawfully processing your  
personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority.  
You can find their contact details here: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/dataprotection/>bodies/authorities/index_en.htm  
Account Information  
If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account,  
you can:  
■ Log into your account settings and update your user account.  
Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information  
from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud,  
troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal  
requirements.  
Cookies and similar technologies: Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer,  
you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to  
remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites. To opt-out of  
interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Sites visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/> .  
Opting out of email marketing: You can unsubscribe from our marketing email list at any time by clicking  
on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send or by contacting us using the details provided below.  
You will then be removed from the marketing email list – however, we will still need to send you service related  
emails that are necessary for the administration and use of your account. To otherwise opt-out, you  
may:  
■ Note your preferences when you register an account with the site.

 **12\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES**  
Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track  
(“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your  
online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and  
implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser  
signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a  
standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that  
practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy.

 **13\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?**  
In Short: Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your  
personal information.  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are  
California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about  
categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and  
the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately  
preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please  
submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.  
If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Sites, you  
have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Sites. To request removal  
of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email  
address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the  
data is not publicly displayed on the Sites, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or  
comprehensively removed from our systems.

 **14\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS POLICY?**  
In Short: Yes, we will update this policy as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws.  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated  
“Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material  
changes to this privacy policy, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or  
by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy policy frequently to be  
informed of how we are protecting your information.

 **15\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS POLICY?**  
ions or comments about this policy, you may contact our Data Protection Officer  
(DPO), Richard Adams, by email at richard.adams@breach.tv, by phone at 877-806-7227, or by post to:  
Breach Media Services  
Richard Adams  
10800 Lakeline Blvd  
#13101  
Austin, TX 78717  
United States
